

LAUTARO FERRANDI

Cangallo n77
Ciudad autónoma de
Buenos Aires
Argentina



+54(291) - 6 48 23 85



💢 lautaroferrandi@gmail.com



Lautaro Ferrandi



lautaroferrandi

ABOUT MF

I am a creative, artistic and ambitious Film and Video Designer with a talent for thinking outside the box and coming up with innovative ideas and video designs. I graduated with a degree in Film and Video Design from La Plata University, La Plata city, Argentina and subsequently have worked in the video editing industry for the past 4 years. I pride myself in providing excellent service to all stakeholders and seeing the positive impact I make in people's lives and businesses. On the other hand, I am eager to learn more and open to new ideas in order to find the best way to achieve the client needs.

EDUCATION

 2013 - 2019
 La Plata National University -Master of Arts (MA) in Film and Media Studies.

La Plata National University - Professor in Film and Media Studies.

COURSES

2019 Cinema4D. Extension Department, School of Arts,
 (March-July) La Plata National University.

 2021 (February- June)
 Diseño UX/UI - CoderHouse.

EXPERIENCES

• 2018 - CreativaPastel - Video Editor.

2018 - 2018 Mobile World Congress (Barcelona) - Social relationships.

2017 - AfonicoMusic - Content Producer, Video Editor.

• 2015 - NuevosVientos - Content Producer, Video Editor.

2017 - Solvay Indupa - Freelance English Translator.

LAGUAJES

English Level: Advanced.

Spanish Level: Native.

SOFTWARE SKILLS